面试
你好 我和尤尔曼先生有约
Hi. I've got an appointment with Mr. Ullman.
我的名字是杰克·特朗斯
My name is Jack Torrance.
他的办公室在一楼的左边
His office is the first door on the left.
谢谢
Thank you.
尤尔曼先生?
Mr. Ullman?
我是杰克·特朗斯
I'm Jack Torrance.
快进来 杰克
Come on in, Jack.
- 非常高兴见到你 - 我也是
- Very nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
这是我的秘书 苏西
This is my secretary, Susie.
- 苏西 你好 - 我们这儿很难找吧?
- Susie, how do you do? - Any trouble finding us?
不难找 到这儿我才花了三个半小时
No problem at all. I made the trip in 3 1/2 hours.
算是非常顺利了
That's very good time.
请稍坐一会 杰克
Sit down a minute, Jack.
随意 不要拘束
Just make yourself at home.
要来点咖啡吗?
Like some coffee?
方便的话 我想尝一尝 谢谢
If you're having some, I wouldn't mind. Thanks.
- 苏西 - 好的 先生
- Susie. - Sure.
顺便请比尔·华生过来
And ask Bill Watson to join us.
好的
Yes, I will.
妈妈
Mom?
什么?
Yeah?
你真打算 整个冬天都住那个旅馆吗?
Do you really want to go and live in that hotel for the winter?
当然我愿意
Sure I do.
那一定会很有趣
It'll be lots of fun.
嗯 我也这么认为
Yeah. I guess so.
不过 那儿恐怕没有人可以陪我玩
Anyway, there's hardly anybody to play with around here.
我知道 交新朋友总要花些时间的
I know. lt always takes a little time to make new friends.
嗯 恐怕是
Yeah, I guess so.
托尼怎样想呢?
What about Tony?
他很期待去住那个旅馆 我敢打赌
He's looking forward to the hotel, I bet.
错 我并不期待 特朗斯太太
No, I ain't, Mrs. Torrance.
好了 托尼 不要淘气
Now, come on, Tony. Don't be silly.
我不想去那个地方
I don't want to go there.
你为什么不想去呢?
How come you don't want to go?
只是不想而已
I just don't.
那我们走着瞧
Let's just wait and see.
我相信我们会有个愉快的冬天
We're all going to have a real good time.
比尔 这位是杰克·特朗斯
Bill, I'd like you to meet Jack Torrance.
你好 比尔
How do you do, Bill?
- 非常高兴认识你 - 很荣幸
- Nice to meet you. - Pleasure to meet you.
找个位子坐 比尔 我们开始吧
Grab a chair, Bill. Join in.
杰克准备为我们 在这个冬天照顾遥望旅馆
Jack is going to take care of the Overlook for us this winter.
等我们这边告个段落 你就带他去逛逛
I'd like you to take him around soon as we're through.
好的
Fine.
杰克是位老师
Jack is a schoolteacher.
以前是位老师
Formerly a schoolteacher.
那你现在干什么?
What line of work are you in now?
写作
I'm a writer.
光靠教书 收支还是平衡不了
Teaching's been more or less a way of making ends meet.
对你而言 这是很大的转变吧?
This ought to be quite a change for you.
我正是在寻求转变
I'm looking for a change.
我们在丹佛的人都强烈推荐杰克 而且我立刻就...
Our people in Denver recommended Jack very highly, and for once...
赞成了他们的意见
...I agree with them.
那好 我们讲到哪里了?
Let's see, where were we?
我正打算解说...
I was about to explain...
我们是在5月15号到10月30号营业
...that our season here runs from May 15th to October 30th.
然后我们会歇业 直到下个5月来临
Then we close down completely until the following May.
我可以问问是为什么吗?
Do you mind if I ask why you do that?
就我所见 在这边滑雪将是非常美妙的事
It seems to me that the skiing up here would be fantastic.
那是肯定的 但是 问题在于庞大的开销...
It would be. The problem is the enormous cost...
为此我们必须保持道路通畅
...it would be to keep the road to Sidewinder open.
而道路绵延25英哩
It's a 25-mile stretch of road.
到了冬天 积雪会厚达20英尺
It gets 20 feet of snow during the winter.
要保持道路通畅的话...
There's just no way to make it economically feasible...
实在是没有什么经济效益
...to keep it clear.
自1907年这个地方被修建以来...
When the place was built in 1907...
很少有人对这儿的冬季运动感兴趣的
...there was very little interest in winter sports.
这个地方是因为它的 与世俗隔绝和风光明媚而闻名
This site was chosen for its seclusion and scenic beauty.
当然 不只如此而已
It's certainly got plenty of that.
不错
That's right.
丹佛的人有没有告诉过你...
Did they give you any idea in Denver...
关于这个工作的负担?
...about what the job entails?
只说了个大概
Only in a very general way.
冬季总是难以想像的酷寒
The winters can be fantastically cruel.
工作内容是维修工作 防止带来重大损失...
The basic idea is to cope with the very costly damage...
和其它一些相关的事
...and depreciation which can occur.
其实主要就是要照顾锅炉...
This consists mainly of running the boiler...
每天都要加热 保持旅馆各个角落的温暖...
...heating different parts of the hotel on a daily rotating basis...
如果有损坏发生就要修复...
...repairing damage as it occurs...
持续维护使损坏无法产生
...and doing repairs so the elements can't get a foothold.
这对我而言是没有问题的
That sounds fine to me.
其实上这工作 真的没有什么太高的要求
Physically, it's not a very demanding job.
在这里 冬季唯一真正要克服的...
The only thing that can get a bit trying here during the winter...
是巨大的被隔离感
...is a tremendous sense of isolation.
那正好是我要寻求的东西
That just happens to be exactly what I'm looking for.
我正构思一部新的作品
I'm outlining a new writing project.
五个月的安静生活 正符合我所需
Five months of peace is just what I want.
很好 杰克
That's very good, Jack.
你知道 对某些人...
Because, for some people...
...孤独...
...solitude...
...和隔离...
...and isolation...
...会是一个很大的问题
...can, of itself, become a problem.
对我而言不是
Not for me.
那你的妻子和儿子呢? 你认为他们没问题吧?
How about your wife and son? Do you think they'll take to it?
他们会喜欢的
They'll love it.
很好
Great.
在我把你交给比尔以前...
Before I turn you over to Bill...
我想我还有一件事 不得不和你讲
...there's one other thing I think we should talk about.
不是吓唬人...
Not to sound melodramatic...
不过 这的确会让某些人
...but it's been known to give a few people...
重新考虑能否接受这个工作
...second thoughts about the job.
我很感兴趣
I'm intrigued.
我认为 丹佛的人一定没有提到这个...
I don't suppose they said anything in Denver...
1970年在这儿发生的悲剧
...about the tragedy we had up here during the winter of 1970.
他们的确没有
I don't believe they did.
我的前任...
My predecessor in this job...
雇佣了一个叫查尔斯·格瑞第 担任冬季看管员的工作
...hired a man named Charles Grady as the winter caretaker.
他带着妻子和两个女儿 一个8一个10岁左右
He came up with his wife and 2 little girls of about 8 and 10.
他有着良好的工作记录和介绍人
He had a good employment record, good references.
就我刚才所言 他似乎...
And from what I've been told, he seemed...
就像一个安全正常的人一样
...like a completely normal individual.
但是冬季的某天...
But at some point during the winter...
他肯定受到了巨大的精神折磨
...he must have suffered some kind of a complete mental breakdown.
然后疯狂地...
He ran amuck...
用斧头 杀了全家人
...and killed his family with an ax.
尸体全堆到西翼的一个房间里...
Stacked them neatly in a room in the west wing, and then...
来福枪装了两发子弹 含在嘴里击发
...he put both barrels of his shotgun in his mouth.
警察认为...
The police thought...
那就是以前所谓的幽闭恐慌症
...that it was what the old-timers used to call cabin fever.
一种幽闭式的反应 发生在...
A kind of claustrophobic reaction which can occur...
人被封闭在一起 经过一段相当长时间后
...when people are shut in together over long periods of time.
这个故事...
That is...
实在很刺激
...quite a story.
是的
Yeah, it is.
到现在我还是无法相信 它就发生在这个地方 就是这儿
It's still hard for me to believe it actually happened here.
但是 它的确是
But it did.
我相信你能理解 我为什么要告诉你这些
I think you can appreciate why I wanted to tell you about it.
我当然可以
I certainly can.
我还可以理解 为什么丹佛的人...
I also understand why your people in Denver...
留着这件事 让你来告诉我
...left it for you to tell me.
显然 一些人会退缩...
Obviously, some people can be put off...
不愿意待在发生过这种事的地方
...from staying in a place where something like that happened.
你可以放心 这不会发生在我身上
You can rest assured that's not going to happen with me.
至于我的妻子...
And as far as my wife is concerned...
我确定告诉她以后 她一定会很着迷
...I'm sure she'll be absolutely fascinated when I tell her.
她是个忠实的鬼故事迷...
She's a confirmed ghost story...
...和恐怖片迷
...and horror film addict.
托尼 你认为爸爸会得到那份工作吗?
Tony, do you think Dad'll get the job?
他已经得到了
He already did.
他马上就会打电话告诉温蒂
He's going to phone Wendy up in a few minutes to tell her.
- 嗨 宝贝 - 嗨 亲爱的 事情进行得怎样?
- Hi, babe. - Hi, hon. How's it going?
很好 我还在旅馆里 而且还有许多地方还没去看过
Great. I'm at the hotel and I still have a lot to do.
我认为9点或10点前 我可能到不了家
I don't think I can get home before 9 or 10.
听起来你得到这份工作了
Sounds like you got the job.
嗯 这儿真是个漂亮的地方
Right. It's a beautiful place.
你和丹尼会喜欢上它的
You and Danny are going to love it.
托尼 你为什么不想去那个旅馆?
Tony, why don't you want to go to the hotel?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道的 好了 告诉我吧
You do too know. Now come on, tell me.
不要 我不想告诉你
I don't want to.
求求你
Please.
不要
No.
好了 托尼 告诉我吧
Now, Tony, tell me.
现在睁开眼睛 我来检查
Now, hold your eyes still so I can see.
很好 另一只眼睛
That's good. Now the other one.
乖孩子
Good boy.
好的 丹尼...
Now, Danny...
在你刷牙的时候
...when you were brushing your teeth...
你记得你闻到一些怪味
...do you remember if you smelled anything funny...
或者看见闪光 和其它一些怪东西吗?
...or saw any bright, flashing lights or anything at all strange?
没有
No.
那你记得你在刷牙么?
Do you remember when you were brushing your teeth?
是的
Yes.
那么 刷牙之后呢? 你记得发生过什么事情吗?
What's the next thing you remember after you were brushing your teeth?
妈妈对我说 "醒醒 丹尼 醒醒"
My mom was saying, "Wake up. Wake up, Danny, wake up."
那你能否记得在刷牙前...
Can you remember what you were doing...
你在做些什么吗?
...just before you started brushing your teeth?
和托尼说话
Talking to Tony.
托尼是你的宠物之一吗?
Is Tony one of your animals?
不是 他是住在我嘴里的小男孩
No. He's a little boy that lives in my mouth.
托尼是他想像中的朋友
Tony's his imaginary friend.
假如你现在张开嘴 我能看见托尼吗?
If you were to open your mouth now, could I see Tony?
为什么不行?
Why not?
因为他藏起来了
Because he hides.
他藏在什么地方?
Where does he go?
我的胃里面
To my stomach.
托尼有要你去做过什么吗?
Does Tony ever tell you to do things?
我不想再谈论托尼了
I don't want to talk about Tony anymore.
好的
That's fine.
好的 丹尼
All right, Danny.
我要请你帮我个忙...
I'm going to ask you to do me a favor...
今天都乖乖地待在床上 好吗?
...and stay quietly in bed for the rest of the day. Okay?
一定要这样吗?
Do I have to?
是的 我希望你这样
Yes. I'd like you to.
我们要去另外的房间说几句话
We're going in the other room for a few minutes and talk.
之后我会来看你的
I'll come back and check on you.
- 我们去客厅吗? - 是的
- Shall we go into the living room? - Yes.
- 请坐 - 谢谢
- Please. - Thank you.
特朗斯太太 我认为你没有什么好担心的
Mrs. Torrance, I don't think you have anything to worry about.
我确信丹尼身体健康
I'm quite sure there's nothing physically wrong with Danny.
他现在看起来非常好
He seems absolutely fine now.
但是你还是应该检查一下
But you should've seen him.
我知道
I know.
孩子往往会吓着你
Kids can scare you to death.
但是相信我 那些并不算反常
But believe me, these episodes are not at all uncommon.
他们往往比表面看起来要好很多
And they look much worse than they are.
但是 他到底是怎么了?
But what was the matter with him?
大多数时候 发生在小孩子身上 某些事情是无法依常理解释的
Most of the time, these episodes with kids are never explained.
只是一些情绪上的原因 而且基本上很少再发生
They're brought on by emotional factors and rarely occur again.
和自我催眠很相似...
They're more akin to autohypnosis...
一种自我诱导的恍惚状态
...a kind of self-induced trance.
但是 假如再发生的话 我认为...
If it reoccurs, which I doubt...
我们可以试着做些检查
...we can always think about having some tests done.
我确信你是对的
I'm sure you're right.
你住在博得很久了吗?
Have you been in Boulder long?
只有三个月左右
Only about three months.
我们是佛蒙得州来的 我丈夫以前在那边的学校教书
We're from Vermont. My husband was teaching school there.
丹尼想像中的朋友出现在...
Did the appearance of Danny's imaginary friend....
托尼
Tony.
那么 托尼的情况 最早发生在你们到这儿的时候吗?
Did Tony's first appearance happen to coincide with your arrival here?
我想想...
Let's see....
丹尼和托尼说话...
I guess Danny started talking to Tony...
是在我们送他去幼儿园时开始的
...about the time we put him in nursery school.
他适应学校生活吗?
Did he adjust well to school?
他最开始并不喜欢学校
He didn't like it too much at first.
但是 之后他受了伤 然后我们就把他留在家里一段时间...
Then he had an injury, so we kept him out for a while and....
这就是我最早 注意到他和托尼交谈的时候
I guess that's about when I first noticed he was talking to Tony.
他受了什么样的伤?
What sort of injury did he have?
肩膀脱臼
He dislocated his shoulder.
他怎么会受这样的伤?
How did he manage to do that?
这只是 嗯 那样的一些事 你知道的
It was just one of those things, you know.
完全是意外事故
Purely an accident.
我丈夫喝醉...
My husband had been drinking...
然后比往常迟三个小时回到家
...and he came home about three hours late.
他那天晚上 心情不太好
So he wasn't exactly in the greatest mood that night.
然后丹尼把他一些教学用试卷 扔到满屋都是...
And Danny had scattered some of his school papers all over the room...
于是我丈夫就拉住他的肩膀 想让他离开那些试卷
...and my husband grabbed his arm to pull him away from them.
就是这样一些行为 你起码对孩子做过上百次...
It's just the sort of thing you do 100 times with a child...
你知道的 平常在公园或者街道上
...you know, in a park or in the street.
但是当时有点失控...
But on this particular occasion...
我丈夫用力过猛
...my husband just used too much strength...
然后他伤着了丹尼的肩膀
...and he injured Danny's arm.
无论如何 负面的事也有一些正面意义 因为他说...
Anyway, something good did come out of it all because he said...
"温蒂 我绝对不会再犯同样的傻事
..."Wendy, I'm never going to touch another drop.
假如再发生的话 你可以离开我"
And if I do, you can leave me."
然后 他的确做到了
And he didn't.
他五个月没再沾过一点酒精
He hasn't had any alcohol in 5 months.
旅馆歇业日
我们肯定到了很高的地方 空气都不太一样了
We must really be high up. The air feels so different.
爸爸?
Dad?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
你应该吃了早餐的
You should've eaten your breakfast.
等我们到了旅馆就给你找些吃的
We'll get you something as soon as we get to the hotel.
好的 妈妈
Okay, Mom.
就是在这附近 多纳组织被雪给困住的吧?
Wasn't it around here that the Donner party got snowbound?
我认为是在更西边的地方 在山脊地带
I think that was farther west, in the Sierras.
什么是多纳组织?
What was the Donner party?
他们是一个蓬车时代的殖民组织
They were a party of settlers in covered wagon times.
某个冬天他们被雪困在山里头
They got snowbound one winter in the mountains.
导致后来他们相互残杀当作食物 为的是让自己能够生存下来
They had to resort to cannibalism in order to stay alive.
你的意思是他们相互吃掉别人?
You mean they ate each other up?
为了活命 他们不得不这样做
They had to, in order to survive.
杰克
Jack.
不要担心 妈妈
Don't worry, Mom.
我知道人吃人的 在电视上看过
I know all about cannibalism. I saw it on TV.
看 我说没什么吧
See, it's okay.
他在电视上都看过了
He saw it on the television.
- 飞机什么时候起飞? - 8点30分
- What time does the plane leave? - 8:30.
这样我们就有充足的时间 可以仔细检查每样东西
That gives us plenty of time to go over everything.
- 再见 尤尔曼先生 - 再见
- Goodbye, Mr. Ullman. - Bye.
早安 希望没有让你等太久
Good morning. I hope you haven't been waiting too long.
没关系 我们正好有足够的时间去找点吃的
No problem. We had time to grab a bite to eat.
很幸运 你能赶在他们关掉厨房前这样做
Good. Glad you made it before they shut down the kitchen.
你的家人都有四处看看吗?
Is your family having a look around?
没有 因为我儿子发现了游戏室
No, my son's discovered the games room.
- 你的行李都带来了吗? - 都在这儿
- Has your luggage been brought in? - Right there.
预见到我们今天要做的一切...
In view of all we have to cover today...
我建议我们去看看你的住所 马上去
...I suggest we have a quick look at your apartment and get started.
把特朗斯先生全家的行李 搬到他们的住所去
Have the Torrances' things brought to their apartment.
我最好先叫上我的家人
I'd better collect my family first.
这是我们的休闲室
This is our Colorado Lounge.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
天!
My God!
这个地方实在太不可思议了 不是吗 亲爱的?
This place is fantastic, isn't it, hon?
的确是
It sure is.
我从来没见过这样的东西
I've never seen anything like this before.
那些全部是正统印地安风格吗?
Are all these lndian designs authentic?
我相信它们是主要是...
I believe they're based...
基于纳瓦霍和阿帕契部族的风格
...mainly on Navajo and Apache motifs.
它们真是非常的华丽
They're really gorgeous.
事实上...
As a matter of fact...
这可能是我所见过的最华丽的旅馆了
...this is probably the most gorgeous hotel I've ever seen.
这个古老的地方有一个辉煌的过去
This old place has had an illustrious past.
在全盛时期 乘喷射机旅行的富豪 都当这里是重要观光景点
In its heyday, it was a stopping place for the jet setters...
甚至在喷射客机旅行流行以前
...even before anybody knew what a jet set was.
这里曾经有四位总统呆过
We had four presidents who stayed here.
很多的影视明星
Lots of movie stars.
皇族呢?
Royalty?
所有最出色的人
All the best people.
这是旅馆职员的宿舍
This is the staff wing of the hotel.
冬天里这里以外的房间都没有暖气
None of the other bedrooms are heated during the winter.
- 再见 尤尔曼先生 - 再见 姑娘们
- Goodbye, Mr. Ullman. - Goodbye, girls.
这里便是你们的居室
And here are your quarters.
客厅 卧室 浴室
Living room, bedroom, bathroom.
还有一间小房间 给你的儿子住
And a small bedroom for your son.
对孩子而言 这相当不错
Perfect for a child.
嗯 这里什么东西都很齐全
Well, then. Place is very nicely self-contained.
比较好管理
Easy to keep.
很舒适
Cozy.
是的 对一个家庭而言 非常舒适
Yes, very cozy for a family.
假如你们想继续的话...
If you feel like spreading out...
要知道 你们还得去看看其它的那些地方
...you have the rest of the hotel to move around in.
嗯 这里非常的...
Well, it's very...
有家的感觉
...homey.
这是我们著名的树篱迷宫
This is our famous hedge maze.
这是非常有吸引力的所在 墙高是13英尺
It's quite an attraction here. The walls are 13 feet high...
还有这些树篱 它们就像这个旅馆一样历史悠久
...and the hedge is as old as the hotel itself.
非常有趣 不过 我绝对不想走进去...
A lot of fun, but I wouldn't want to go in there...
除非我自己有把握 一个小时内能走出来
...unless I had an hour to spare to find my way out.
遥望旅馆是什么时候修建的?
When was the Overlook built?
1907年开始建造
Construction started in 1907.
1909年竣工
It was finished in 1909.
地基据说是印地安人的墓地
The site's supposed to be on an lndian burial ground.
这一度激怒了他们...
They actually had to repel...
甚至在修建过程中 遭遇过印地安人的攻击
...a few lndian attacks as they were building it.
这是我们的雪地车
That's our Snowcat.
你们两个都会开吧?
Can you both drive a car?
很好 一般说来 开雪地车就跟开普通车辆没两样
That's fine. Basically the Snowcat operates very much like a car.
你不会花太多时间来掌握它的
It won't take you long to get the hang of it.
事实上 我们曾经从芝加哥找了个漆匠...
As a matter of fact, we brought a decorator in from Chicago...
就在去年 重新粉刷旅馆的这个部分
...just last year to refurbish this part of the hotel.
他的确做的非常漂亮
He sure did a beautiful job.
粉红和金色是我最喜欢的色彩
Pink and gold are my favorite colors.
这是我们的黄金舞厅
This is our Gold Ballroom.
哇塞!
I'll say!
我们可以让300人在这里舒适地聚会
We can accommodate up to 300 people here very comfortably.
哈 我们可以在这里开个精采的派对
Boy, we could really have a good party in this room.
我恐怕 在你获得补给品之前 此处也不真能让你开个好派对
I'm afraid you won't do too well here unless you brought supplies.
在关闭前 我们会把酒从柜台那边移走
We remove the booze from the premises when we shut down.
这将减低我们的保险费用
That reduces the insurance we normally have to carry.
我们并不喝酒
We don't drink.
那么 你们非常幸运
Then you're in luck.
迪克 过来跟特朗斯太太和先生问个好
Dick, come on over and say hello to Mr. and Mrs. Torrance.
这是迪克·哈罗朗 我们的首席厨师
This is Dick Hallorann, our head chef.
哈罗朗先生 我是杰克 这是我的妻子 温妮芙瑞德
Mr. Hallorann, I'm Jack. This is my wife, Winifred.
很高兴认识你
Glad to meet you.
特朗斯一家人 将在这个冬季照顾遥望旅馆
The Torrances will take care of the Overlook this winter.
这很好啊 你们对我们的旅馆印象如何?
That's just great. How do you folks like our hotel so far?
非常棒的地方
It's just wonderful.
嗨 丹尼!
Hi, Danny!
我刚好在外面遇上他 他在找你们
I found him outside looking for you.
你已经厌倦玩游戏了?
Did you get tired of bombing the universe?
到这边来
Come on over here.
谢谢你 苏西
Thank you, Susie.
你应该带特朗斯太太去看一下厨房
I think it'd be good if you could show Mrs. Torrance the kitchen...
我和杰克可以继续逛逛
...while I continue on with Jack.
那是我的荣幸 请这边走
It would be a pleasure. Right this way.
好的 一会见 亲爱的
Great. See you later, honey.
再见 亲爱的
Bye, darling.
特朗斯太太 你丈夫介绍你说名字叫温妮芙瑞德
Mrs. Torrance, your husband introduced you as Winifred.
那么 是叫你"温妮"还是"芙瑞蒂"?
Now, are you a "Winnie", or a "Freddie"?
叫我温蒂
I'm a Wendy.
温蒂 不错 非常好的称呼
Wendy. That's nice. That's the prettiest.
这里就是厨房吗?
This is the kitchen, huh?
是的
This is it.
你喜欢这里吗 丹尼? 对你而言 这里够大了吗?
How do you like it, Danny? is it big enough for you?
这是我见过的最大的地方
It's the biggest place I ever seen.
这整个地方就像个巨大的迷宫
This whole place is such an enormous maze.
我每次进来都得撒些面包屑做标记
I'll have to leave a trail of breadcrumbs every time I come in.
不要让它把你吓倒了
Don't let it get you down.
它是很大 不过无论怎样也只是间厨房而已
It's big, but it ain't nothing but a kitchen.
这里许多东西你都没必要去碰
A lot of this stuff you'll never have to touch.
如果乱碰 我将很难收拾
I wouldn't know what to do with it if I did.
有一件事是肯定的 你不要担心没有食物
One thing for sure, you don't have to worry about food.
足够你们在这儿吃一年 而且保证每次的菜单都不一样
You folks could eat here for a year and never have the same menu twice.
这里是我们的冷藏室
Right here is our walk-in freezer.
我们在这里存放肉类
This is where we keep all of our meat.
这里有15块烘干的排骨...
You got 15 rib roasts...
30袋汉堡 每袋10磅...
...30 ten-pound bags of hamburger.
还有12只火鸡 大约40只鸡...
We got 12 turkeys, about 40 chickens...
50份牛排 2打猪排...
...50 sirloin steaks, two dozen of pork roast...
还有20条羔羊腿 你喜欢羔羊吧 多克?
...and 20 legs of lamb. Do you like lamb, Doc?
不喜欢? 那 你最喜欢的是什么食物呢?
You don't? What's your favorite food, then?
法国油炸食物和调味酱
French fries and ketchup.
我想我们也能找到那个的 多克
I think we can manage that too, Doc.
继续走 小心你们的脚下
Come along, now. Watch your step.
你怎么知道我们叫他多克?
How'd you know we call him Doc?
- 你什么意思? - 多克 你叫了丹尼两次"多克"
- Beg your pardon? - Doc. You called Danny "Doc" twice.
我有吗?
I did?
我们有时叫他多克 就像卡通片 "疯狂的兔子" 里一样
We call him Doc sometimes, like in the Bugs Bunny cartoons.
但是 你是怎么知道的呢?
But how did you know?
我想 我可能是听到你这么叫他了
I guess I probably heard you call him that.
有可能 但是我真的不记得...
It's possible. But I honestly don't remember...
在我们见面后我有这么叫过他
...calling him that since we've been with you.
无论如何 他看起来就像是多克 不是么?
Anyway, he looks like a Doc, doesn't he?
怎么了 多克?
What's up, Doc?
嗯 这里是储藏室
Now, this is the storeroom.
在这里我们存放...
In here is where we keep...
所有的干料和罐头
...all the dried goods and the canned goods.
我们有罐装的水果和蔬菜...
We got canned fruits and vegetables...
罐装的鱼和肉食 还有其它一些粮食
...canned fish and meats, hot and cold cereals.
比如面包片 薯片 甜点...
Post Toasties, Corn Flakes, Sugar Puffs...
爆米花 麦片 还有小麦油
...Rice Krispies, oatmeal, Wheatena and Cream of Wheat.
还有成打的黑枫糖...
You got a dozen jugs of black molasses.
60箱牛奶...
We got 60 boxes of dried milk...
你想要些冰淇淋吗 多克?
How'd you like some ice cream, Doc?
各种小吃 甜点...
Sociables, finger rolls...
你想要的每种食物
...and 7 kinds of what have you.
嗯 我们有桃干 杏干...
Now, we've got dried peaches, dried apricots...
...葡萄干和李干
...dried raisins and dried prunes.
你知道 如果你想快乐一点 你必须要保持秩序
You know, you got to keep regular if you want to be happy.
- 你们进行得怎样? - 很好
- How're you getting on? - Fine.
能借用一下特朗斯太太吗? 我们正打算去地下室
Can we borrow Mrs. Torrance? We're on our way to the basement.
我保证不会占用很长时间的
I promise we won't keep her very long.
好的 尤尔曼先生 我正打算去做冰淇淋的
No problem, Mr.Ullman. I was just getting to the ice cream.
你喜欢冰淇淋吧 多克?
You like ice cream, Doc?
我认为你喜欢呢
I thought you did.
你们介意在等你们的这段时间 我给丹尼一些冰淇淋么?
You folks mind if I give Danny some ice cream while we wait?
- 当然不会 - 我们不介意的
- Not at all. - We don't mind.
- 好的 - 听到这个你很高兴吧 多克?
- Good. - Sound good to you, Doc?
好吧 你们去做你们的
Okay, you behave yourself.
你想要哪种冰淇淋呢?
What kind of ice cream do you like?
巧克力
Chocolate.
那就是巧克力的 来吧 孩子 过来
Chocolate it shall be. Come on, son.
今天真是非常神奇的一天
It's amazing, all this activity today.
客人和部分职员昨天就走了 但是...
The guests and some staff left yesterday, but the...
这最后一天仍然是令人兴奋的
...last day's always hectic.
每个人都想尽早上路
Everybody wants to be on their way as early as possible.
今晚5点后 就很难想像 这个地方有很多人在的样子
By 5:00 tonight, you'll never know anybody was ever here.
就像艘鬼船一样 不是吗?
Just like a ghost ship, huh?
你晓得为什么 我知道你的名字叫多克吗?
Do you know how I knew your name was Doc?
你不明白我在说什么吧?
You know what I'm talking about, don't you?
我记得 在我还小的时候...
I can remember when I was a little boy...
...我的祖母和我可以...
...my grandmother and I could hold conversations...
...完全不开口进行交谈
...entirely without ever opening our mouths.
她管这叫"闪灵"
She called it "shining."
一直以来 我都认为只有我和她...
And for a long time I thought it was just the two of us...
拥有"闪灵"
...that had "the shine" to us.
就像你也可能 一直认为自己有独特天赋一样
Just like you probably thought you was the only one.
但是 还有其他人也是一样的...
But there are other folks...
虽然他们大多数都没有体会到 甚至不相信
...though mostly they don't know it, or don't believe it.
你能这样已经多久了?
How long have you been able to do it?
你为什么不想谈谈它呢?
Why don't you want to talk about it?
我不该那样
I'm not supposed to.
谁说你不该那样?
Who says you ain't supposed to?
托尼
Tony.
谁是托尼?
Who's Tony?
托尼是住在我嘴里的小男孩
Tony's the little boy that lives in my mouth.
托尼就是那个...
Is Tony the one that...
告诉你古怪事情的人?
...tells you things?
他怎样告诉你的?
How does he tell you things?
我就像是睡着了一样 然后 他就给我看一些东西
It's like I go to sleep, and he shows me things.
但是 当我醒来后 我就记不起来发生了什么
But when I wake up, I can't remember everything.
你父母知道托尼的事吗?
Does your mom and dad know about Tony?
- 他们知道 - 托尼有告诉你奇怪的事情吗?
- Yes. - Do they know he tells you things?
不知道 托尼叫我绝对不要和他们说
No, Tony told me never to tell them.
托尼有告诉过你这个地方的事吗?
Has Tony ever told you anything about this place?
关于遥望旅馆?
About the Overlook Hotel?
我不知道
I don't know.
仔细想想 多克
Now think real hard, Doc.
想想
Think.
他似乎有给我看过一些东西
Maybe he showed me something.
那 仔细想想是什么
Try to think of what it was.
哈罗朗先生 你害怕这个地方吗?
Mr. Hallorann, are you scared of this place?
不怕 并不害怕
No, Scared of nothing here.
只是...
It's just that...
你知道的 一些地方 似乎就像人一样
...you know, some places are like people.
有的很特别...
Some shine...
但 有的却相反
...and some don't.
我想遥望旅馆...
I guess you could say the Overlook Hotel...
它有些东西 很特别 就像闪灵一样
...has something about it that's like shining.
这里有发生过不好的事吗?
Is there something bad here?
你知道 多克 一些事发生后...
You know, Doc, when something happens...
它总会留下一些痕迹
...it can leave a trace of itself behind.
嗯 就像...
Say, like...
大胡子会在胡须上留下面包屑
...if someone burns toast.
但是 某些事情却留下不一样的痕迹
Maybe things that happen leave other kind of traces behind.
不是所有人都可以注意到的那种痕迹
Not things that anyone can notice.
但是 拥有闪灵的人可以看到
But things that people who shine can see.
就像他们能看到还没发生的事一样...
Just like they can see things that haven't happened yet...
在某些时候 他们能看到许久以前发生的一些事
...sometimes they can see things that happened a long time ago.
我想 这里曾经发生过许多事...
I think a lot of things happened right here...
在这所特别的旅馆的悠久历史里
...in this particular hotel over the years.
这些事 并不全都是好事
And not all of them was good.
那么 237房发生过什么?
What about room 237?
237房?
Room 237?
你害怕237房 不是吗?
You're scared of room 237, ain't you?
不怕 我不害怕
No, I ain't.
哈罗朗先生 237房里面到底有些什么?
Mr. Hallorann, what is in room 237?
什么也没有
Nothing.
237房里面没有什么 根本没有!
There ain't nothing in room 237.
而且 你也没有必要去那个地方
But you ain't got no business going in there anyway.
所以 不要靠近它
So stay out.
明白了吗? 不要靠近它!
You understand? Stay out!
一个月后
早晨 亲爱的
Good morning, hon.
你的早餐已经做好了
Your breakfast is ready.
现在几点?
What time is it?
大概11点30分
It's about 11:30.
天啊
Jesus.
我想我们实在是睡得太晚
I guess we've been staying up too late.
我知道
I know it.
都按你喜欢的口味做的 尝尝吧
I made them just the way you like them, sunny-side up.
很好
Nice.
外面的风景真的很美
It's really pretty outside.
吃完早餐后 我们可以出去散步么?
How about taking me for a walk after you finish your breakfast?
我想我得先写些东西
I suppose I ought to try to do some writing first.
有什么构思了吗?
Any ideas yet?
太多的构思
Lots of ideas.
但是都没有好的
No good ones.
好创意总会有的
Something will come.
关键是要养成每天都得写作的习惯
It's just a matter of settling into the habit of writing every day.
就是这样而已
That's all it is.
到这个地方来真是不错啊 不是吗?
It's really nice up here, isn't it?
我喜欢这儿
I love it.
真的喜欢
I really do.
我从来没有在别的地方 感觉有这么舒适和快活
I've never been this happy or comfortable anywhere.
你这么快就能适应这样一个大地方 真是让人惊讶
It's amazing how fast you get used to such a big place.
老实说 我们刚来的时候...
I tell you, when we first came up here...
我认为这里会非常可怕
...I thought it was kind of scary.
但是我立刻就喜欢上了这儿
I fell in love with it right away.
当我来这里应聘的时候...
When I came up here for my interview...
就感到 我似乎曾经来过这儿
...it was as though I'd been here before.
我的意思是 我们总会有些似曾相识的感觉...
I mean, we all have moments of deja vu...
但是这次有些不一样
...but this was ridiculous.
我几乎能知道...
It was almost as though I knew...
每个角落会有些什么东西存在
...what was going to be around every corner.
输了的人就要打扫整个美国 怎样?
The loser has to keep America clean. How's that?
- 好的 - 你已经要输了
- All right. - And you're going to lose.
我要来抓你了 你最好跑快点!
And I'm going to get you. You'd better run fast!
注意了!
Look out!
我快抓到你了
I'm coming in close.
输家要打扫整个美国哦
Loser has to keep America clean.
我要打扫整个美国
Keep America clean.
丹尼 你赢了
Danny, you win.
我们休息会吧 走走
Let's take the rest of this walking.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
这里很漂亮吧?
Isn't it beautiful?
死胡同
Dead end.
我们到了
We made it.
很漂亮吧?
Isn't it beautiful?
非常漂亮
It's so pretty.
我没有想到它居然这么大 你呢?
I didn't think it was going to be this big. Did you?
没有
No.
星期二
卢瑟福在追查一起...
Rutherford was serving a life sentence...
在1968年执行枪决的命案
...for a 1968 shooting.
对在阿斯本失踪妇女的搜索 仍然持续进行着
And the search continues for that missing Aspen woman.
苏珊·罗伯逊 24岁 已经失踪10天了
24-year-old Susan Robertson has been missing 10 days.
她在和丈夫一起的打猎途中走失
She disappeared on a hunting trip with her husband.
他们也许不得不取消搜索...
They may have to call off the search...
假如预测的暴风雪明天果真来临
...if a predicted snowstorm moves in tomorrow.
丹佛今天风和日丽...
It's so beautiful in Denver today...
很难想像一场暴风雪就要来临
...it's hard to believe a snowstorm could be close.
我甚至想出去沐浴阳光...
I want to go outside and lie in the sun...
在我们的北方和西方 天气仍然很冷 下着雪
...yet to our north, to our west, it is snowing and cold.
而且冷空气在移动...
And it's moving...
这同时 它正移向科罗拉多州 难以置信...
...right here towards Colorado as we talk. It's incredible.
嗨 亲爱的
Hi, honey.
工作进行得怎样?
How's it going?
还行
Fine.
今天写了很多吗?
Get a lot written today?
是的
Yes.
天气预报说 今晚会开始下雪
The weather forecast said it's going to snow tonight.
那又怎样? 你想我怎样?
What do you want me to do about it?
好了 亲爱的
Come on, honey.
不用这么不高兴吧
Don't be so grouchy.
我并没有...
I'm not...
不高兴
...being grouchy.
我只是想完成我的工作
I just want to finish my work.
好的 我明白了
Okay. I understand.
一会儿我给你带点三明治来
I'll come back later with a couple of sandwiches.
到那时候 你也许能让我看看 你已经写了些什么
Maybe you'll let me read something then.
温蒂...
Wendy...
...让我告诉你一件事
...let me explain something to you.
当你进来打断我的时候 意味着你破坏了我的集中力
When you come in and interrupt, you're breaking my concentration.
你把我的注意力转移开了...
You're distracting me...
我得费力气 再把注意力摆回工作上去
...and it will then take me time to get back to where I was.
明白了吗?
Understand?
明白
Yeah.
好的
Fine.
我们得定个新规矩:
We're going to make a new rule:
无论什么时候 只要我在这里...
Whenever I'm in here...
你有听到我打字的声音...
...and you hear me typing...
或者 无论你听到我在这里干什么
...or whatever the fuck you hear me doing in here...
只要我呆在这儿 就意味着我在工作
...when I'm in here, that means I am working.
也就是说 那时不能进来打扰我
That means don't come in.
好了 你现在明白了吗?
Now, do you think you can handle that?
- 嗯 - 好
- Yeah. - Fine.
那你怎么还不行动 给我滚出这个地方?
Why don't you start right now and get the fuck out of here?
好
Okay.
星期四
你好了吧!
All right, you!
你知道你手里面还有
I know you've got more.
没打中!
Missed!
现在没了!
Don't have!
那不怕你了
No fair anymore.
星期六
我应该早想到
I knew it.
这是KDK 12在呼叫KDK 1
This is KDK 12 calling KDK 1.
KDK 12 呼叫 KDK 1
KDK 12 to KDK 1.
这边是KDK 1 我们收到你的呼叫了 完毕
This is KDK 1. We're receiving you. Over.
嗨 我是遥望旅馆的温蒂·特朗斯
Hi, this is Wendy Torrance at the Overlook Hotel.
嗨 你们在上头过得如何? 完毕
Hi, how are you folks getting on up there? Over.
我们过得很好
We're just fine.
但是我们的电话 似乎有点问题
But our telephones aren't doing too well.
是线路断了吗? 完毕
Are the lines down, by any chance? Over.
是的 因为暴风雪的关系 一部分线路出问题了 完毕
Yes, quite a few of them are down due to the storm. Over.
有可能尽快修好吗? 完毕
Any chance of them being repaired soon? Over.
嗯 我恐怕不行
Well, I wouldn't like to say.
可能整个冬天都只能这样 得等到春天才会修理 完毕
Most winters they stay that way until spring. Over.
伙计 这暴风雪可真是厉害 不是吗? 完毕
Boy, this storm is really something, isn't it? Over.
是的 真是如此
Yes. It's one of the worst we've had for years.
我们还能为你做点其它的什么吗? 特朗斯太太 完毕
Is there anything else we can do for you, Mrs. Torrance?
我想 没什么了 完毕
I suppose not. Over.
假如你们遇到什么麻烦 就呼叫我们
If you folks have any problems up there, just give us a call.
还有 特朗斯太太...
And, Mrs. Torrance?
你们最好一直都开着无线通话装置
It might be a good idea if you leave your radio on all the time.
好的 我们会这样做的
Okay. We'll do that.
很高兴能和你交谈
It was real nice talking to you.
再见 挂断
Bye. Over and out.
你好 丹尼
Hello, Danny.
来和我们一起玩吧
Come and play with us.
和我们一起玩吧 丹尼
Come and play with us, Danny.
永远...
Forever...
...and ever...
永远
...and ever.
托尼...
Tony...
我很害怕
...I'm scared.
记住哈罗朗先生说过的话
Remember what Mr. Hallorann said.
那就像是书里的插画一样 没什么好怕的 丹尼
It's just like pictures in a book, Danny.
那并不是真实的东西
It isn't real.
星期一
请让我给你些钱
Please let me give you some money.
不要 我想我不能接受
I wouldn't think of it.
好的 那你要我怎样报答你?
Well, how can I repay you?
不用了 真的
It's okay. Really.
嗯 我想喝些咖啡
Well, I'm going to have some coffee.
你也喝点好吗?
Would you like some?
好吧
Sure.
很好 请坐
Great. Sit down.
神奇炸圈饼 你自己拿罢
Marvelous doughnuts. Help yourself.
- 咖啡马上就好 - 妈妈
- Coffee will be ready in a few minutes. - Mom.
什么?
Yes.
我能去我的房间拿我的消防车吗?
Can I go up to my room and get my fire engine?
现在不行 爸爸正在睡觉呢
Not right now. Daddy's asleep.
我会小心不出声的
I won't make any noise.
嗯 多克
Now come on, Doc.
你爸爸才睡了一会儿
He only went to bed a few hours ago.
你不能再等等么?
Can't you wait till later?
我不会弄出声响的 我保证 我会掂脚尖走进去
I won't make a sound. I promise I'll tiptoe.
好吧
All right.
但是真的不要弄出声音
But really don't make a sound.
我不会的 妈妈
I won't, Mom.
拿到就马上回来...
Make sure you come right back...
因为我得马上去做午饭了
...because I'm going to make lunch soon.
好的 妈妈
Okay, Mom.
我能去我的房间拿我的消防车吗?
Can I go to my room and get my fire engine?
到这边来
Come here for a minute first.
感觉怎样呢 多克?
How's it going, Doc?
很好
Okay.
过得好吗?
Having a good time?
是的 爸爸
Yes, Dad.
很好
Good.
我希望你能过得愉快
I want you to have a good time.
我很愉快 爸爸
I am, Dad.
- 爸爸 - 什么?
- Dad. - yes?
你感觉不好?
Do you feel bad?
不是 只是有些累
No, I'm just a little bit tired.
那 你为什么不睡会呢?
Then why don't you go to sleep?
我不能睡
I can't.
因为还有很多事得做
I got too much to do.
你喜欢这所旅馆吗?
Do you like this hotel?
嗯
I do.
我喜欢它
I love it.
难道你不是吗?
Don't you?
我想 我也是
I guess so.
很好
Good.
我希望你能喜欢这里
I want you to like it here.
我希望我们能永远待在这个地方...
I wish we could stay here forever...
永远...
...and ever...
永远
...and ever.
什么?
What?
你永远都不会伤害我和妈妈 对吗?
You would never hurt Mommy or me, would you?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你妈妈对你说过些什么?
Did your mother ever say that to you?
说我会伤害你?
That I would hurt you?
没有 爸爸
No, Dad.
你确定?
You sure?
是的 爸爸
Yes, Dad.
我爱你 丹尼
I love you, Danny.
我爱你 胜过一切...
I love you more than anything else...
胜过世上的任何东西...
...in the whole world...
我永远不会伤害你的...
...and I would never do anything to hurt you...
永远
...never.
你知道的 不是吗?
You know that, don't you?
是的 爸爸
Yes, Dad.
很好
Good.
星期三
妈妈
Mom.
妈妈 你在吗?
Mom, are you in there?
怎么了?
What happened?
亲爱的...
Honey...
发生了什么事?
...what's wrong?
我作梦了...
I had the most...
作一个我一生中最可怕的梦
...terrible nightmare I ever had.
- 最最可怕的 - 好了 好了 现在没事了
- It was the most horrible dream. - It's okay, it's okay now.
真的?
Really.
我梦见...
I dreamed that I...
我杀了你和丹尼
...that I killed you and Danny.
但是 我不仅仅是杀了你们
But I didn't just kill you.
我还把你们切成一片一片的
I cut you up into little pieces.
我的天
My God.
我一定是疯了
I must be losing my mind.
一切都会没事的
Everything's going to be all right.
好的 让我们站起来
Come on. Let's get up off the floor.
坐下
There. Now sit up.
好的
It's okay.
放松
丹尼!
Danny!
没什么事
Everything's okay!
去你的房间玩会儿
Just go play in your room for a while.
你爸爸有些头痛
Your dad's just got a headache.
丹尼 听到我说什么了吗? 去你房间里玩
Danny, mind what I say. Go play in your room.
亲爱的 等我把他带走
Honey, let me just go get him out of here.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
你为什么不听我的话?
Why don't you mind me?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
你脖子上是怎么搞的?
What happened to your neck?
你脖子上到底是怎么回事?
你对他这样的...
You did this to him...
不是你吗?
...didn't you?!
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch!
你居然这样对他!
You did this to him!
你居然? !
Didn't you?!
你怎么可以这样? !
How could you?!
你怎么忍心? !
我得来点喝的 无论要我付出什么代价
God! I'd give anything for a drink.
即便付出我该死的灵魂...
I'd give my goddamn soul...
能换来一杯啤酒
...for just a glass of beer.
嗨 罗伊德
Hi, Lloyd.
今晚似乎没什么人 不是吗?
A little slow tonight, isn't it?
是的 特朗斯先生
Yes it is, Mr. Torrance.
想要点什么?
What will it be?
这个问题你问得好 罗伊德...
I'm awfully glad you asked me that, Lloyd...
因为我正好有两张20块
...because I just happen to have two twenties...
和两张10块的钞票摆在我口袋里
...and two tens right here in my wallet.
我正担心 它们会在口袋里待到下个春天呢
I was afraid they were going to be there until next April.
好 听着 我要的是:
So here's what:
你给我一瓶波本...
You slip me a bottle of bourbon...
和一个装了冰块的杯子
...a little glass and some ice.
你能做到吧 不是吗 罗伊德?
You can do that, can't you, Lloyd?
你并不很忙 是吧?
You're not too busy, are you?
是的 先生 我一点都不忙
No, sir. I'm not busy at all.
好伙计
Good man.
你把它们摆好...
You set them up...
我会把它们各个击破
...and I'll knock them back, one by one.
白人的使命 罗伊德 我的伙计
White man's burden, Lloyd, my man.
白人的使命 (暗指: 击退印地安人)
White man's burden.
我说 罗伊德...
Say, Lloyd...
我好像一时有点轻飘飘了
...it seems I'm temporarily light.
不管怎么说 我在这边信誉如何?
How's my credit in this joint, anyway?
你的信誉很好 特朗斯先生
Your credit's fine, Mr. Torrance.
我可以发誓
That's swell.
我欣赏你 罗伊德
I like you, Lloyd.
我一直都欣赏你
I always liked you.
你是其中最优秀的
You were always the best of them.
好得不能再好的吧台招待...
Best goddamned bartender...
从蒂姆布克图到缅因州的波特兰
...from Timbuktu to Portland, Maine.
或是到俄勒冈州的波特兰 都是一样的
Or Portland, Oregon, for that matter.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you for saying so.
在货车上过了备受煎熬的5个月...
Here's to 5 miserable months on the wagon...
给我带来了永久的心灵创伤
...and all the irreparable harm that it's caused me.
过得还顺利吧? 特朗斯先生
How are things going, Mr. Torrance?
情况会好转的
Things could be better.
情况会整个彻底好转的
Things could be a whole lot better.
我希望没什么太大问题
I hope it's nothing serious.
没什么大问题啦
Nothing serious.
只是跟楼上的哪个老精子银行(注:温蒂) 有点小小问题
Just a little problem with...the old sperm bank upstairs.
但我完全可以掌握
Nothing I can't handle, though.
谢谢
Thanks.
女人
Women.
不能够和她们一起生活...
Can't live with them...
离开她们又活不下去
...can't live without them.
智慧金言 罗伊德
Words of wisdom, Lloyd.
智慧...
Words of...
良言
...wisdom.
我绝没有碰他 妈的
I never laid a hand on him, goddamn it.
我没有
I didn't.
连一根寒毛都没去碰
I wouldn't touch one hair on his goddamn little head.
我爱那个小王八蛋
I love the little son of a bitch.
我会为他做任何事
I'd do anything for him.
他妈的任何事情
Any fucking thing for him.
但那个婊子!
But that bitch!
只要我还活着...
As long as I live...
她就不会让我忘记发生过的事
...she'll never let me forget what happened.
我确实伤害过他一次 好不好?
I did hurt him once, okay?
单纯的意外
It was an accident.
完全不算故意的
Completely unintentional.
任何人遇到那种事 都可能那样反应
It could have happened to anybody.
而且 他妈的 都过去三个年头了!
And it was three goddamn years ago!
那小杂碎把我的稿纸扔满地
The little fucker had thrown all my papers all over the floor.
我只是想把他拉起来
All I tried to do was pull him up.
一时肌肉动作失去协调
A momentary loss of muscular coordination.
我是说...
I mean...
力道多出几磅...
...a few extra foot-pounds of energy...
平均每秒 每秒才...
...per second, per second.
感谢上帝你在这里
Thank God you're here.
旅馆里除了我们 还有另一个人在
There's someone else in the hotel with us.
其中一间房子里有个疯女人
There's a crazy woman in one of the rooms.
她想把丹尼掐死
She tried to strangle Danny.
你他妈的神智不清了?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
那是真的 真的!
It's the truth! Really.
我发誓 丹尼告诉我的
I swear it. Danny told me.
他上去 进入其中一间卧房
He went up into one of the bedrooms.
门是开着的 他看见这疯女人在浴缸里
The door was open, and he saw this crazy woman in the bathtub.
她想把他掐死!
She tried to strangle him!
在哪个房间?
Which room was it?
来自迈阿密的10频道
From Channel 10 in Miami...
这里是新闻观察和格兰林克...
...this is Newswatch with Glen Rinker...
安毕雪与广受好评的新闻观察小组
...Ann Bishop, and the award- winning Newswatch team.
晚安 我是10频道新闻观察的格兰林克
Good evening. I'm Glen Rinker, Newswatch Ten.
当迈阿密闷热的天气持续刷新记录 冬季的热浪...
As Miami continues to swelter in a record winter heat wave...
带来超过华氏90度的高温...
...bringing temperatures to the 90s...
中部和山区的州区 却被埋在皑皑白雪之中
...Central and Mountain states are buried in snow.
今晚光是科罗拉多 几个小时内就积了10英吋厚的雪
In Colorado, 10 inches of snow fell injust a few hours tonight.
几乎不可能在洛矶山脉从事旅游活动
Travel in the Rockies is almost impossible.
机场被迫关闭 滞留了成千上万的旅客
Airports are shut down, stranding thousands of passengers.
高速公路被雪堆阻挡
Highways are blocked by snowdrifts.
铁轨被冻住
Railroad tracks are frozen.
科罗拉多官方告知新闻观察...
Officials in Colorado tell Newswatch...
已经至少有三个人在寒风中被冻死
...at least 3 have been killed by exposure to freezing winds.
希望科罗拉多政府...
The governor of Colorado is expected...
宣布进入天气警戒状态
...to declare a weather emergency.
应动员全民进行防备...
The National Guard might be called out...
清除街道和公路积雪
...to clear streets and roads.
天气预报 今晚到明天...
Weather forecasters predict more snow...
将有更多的降雪 并伴有强风...
...and heavy winds tonight and tomorrow...
同时温度会降到0度以下
...with temperatures dropping well below zero.
回到佛罗里达 我们碰到了相反的问题
Back here in Florida, we've got the opposite problem.
炎热和潮湿预计会更加恶化
The heat and humidity are supposed to climb.
应该封锁本地的沙滩
Local beaches should bejammed.
我们的气象专家华特克朗斯...
Our weather expert, Walter Cronice...
将在稍后的新闻观察里 为您播报本地天气预报
...will have the local forecast later on Newswatch.
对不起 您所拨的号码无法接通
We're sorry. Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
如果您需要帮助请拨叫接线员
If you need assistance, please call the operator.
- 杰克? - 是 是我
- Jack? - Yes, it's me.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
你找到什么了吗?
Did you find anything?
没有 什么也没有
No. Nothing at all.
我什么见鬼的东西都没看到
I didn't see one goddamn thing.
你去了丹尼说的那间房了吗? 去237?
You went into the room Danny said? To 237?
是的 我去了
Yes, I did.
你什么也没看到?
And you didn't see anything at all?
绝对没有
Absolutely nothing.
他怎么样了?
How is he?
他还在睡
He's still asleep.
好
Good.
我肯定明天早上 他就会回过神来的
I'm sure he'll be himself again in the morning.
你确定就是那个房间吗?
Are you sure it was the right room?
我是说 也许丹尼弄错了
I mean, maybe Danny made a mistake.
他一定就是进去那个房间
He must have gone in that room.
门开着 灯也亮着
The door was open, the lights were on.
我只是弄不明白
I just don't understand it.
他脖子上的伤痕是怎么回事?
What about those bruises on his neck?
有人把他弄成那样的
Somebody did that to him.
我想是...
I think...
他自己弄的
...he did it to himself.
不可能
No.
那不可能
That's not possible.
一旦你排除他对所发生的事情的说法...
Once you rule out his version of what happened...
就再没有其他解释了
...there is no other explanation.
有吗?
Is there?
那和我们来这里前的那次事件...
It wouldn't be that different from the episode...
没有什么不同的
...that he had before we came up here.
不是吗?
Would it?
不管是什么原因...
Whatever the explanation is...
我想我们...
...I think we...
得带丹尼离开这里
...have to get Danny out of here.
带他离开这里?
Get him out of here?
你的意思是...
You mean...
离开这座旅馆?
...just leave the hotel?
制造一个像这样的问题...
It is so...
这正是你的风格
...typical of you to create a problem like this...
当我总算有机会完成什么的时候!
...when I finally have a chance to accomplish something!
当我真正投入我的作品的时候!
When I'm really into my work!
如果现在回去 我真的能写出自己的大作 不是吗?
I could really write my own ticket if I went back now, couldn't I?
铲铲车道 洗洗车子
Shoveling out driveways, work in a car wash.
这类事情很吸引你?
Any of that appeal to you?
到现在我一直让你糟蹋我的生活...
I have let you fuck up my life so far...
这次我不会再让你糟蹋了
...but I am not going to let you fuck this up.
晚安 森林服务台
Good evening. Forest Service.
我叫迪克·霍洛朗
My name is Dick Hallorann.
我是遥望旅馆的厨师长
I'm the head chef at the Overlook Hotel.
晚安 有什么我能为您效劳吗?
Good evening. What can I do for you?
我一直想打个电话到那上面去 很急...
I've been trying to make an urgent phone call up there...
但接线员告诉我线路不通
...but the operator said that the phone lines are down.
这周围的很多线路在暴风雪里都断掉了
A lot of lines around here are down due to the storm.
我不想给您带来任何麻烦...
I hate to put you through any trouble...
但现在有一家人孤零零的在上头 还带着个小孩子
...but there's a family up there all by themselves with a young kid.
又遇到了这场暴风雪 总之...
And with this storm and everything...
如果您能用无线电联系上他们的话 我会非常感激的...
...I'd appreciate it if you'd give them a call on your radio...
只是想看看是不是一切正常
...just to see if everything's okay.
我很乐意这么做
I'll be glad to do that.
你为什么不20分钟后再打给我呢?
Why don't you call me back in about 20 minutes?
非常感谢 我会那样做的
Thank you very much. I'll do that.
好的 先生
All right, sir.
晚安 特朗斯先生
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
晚安
Good evening.
嗨 罗伊德
Hi, Lloyd.
离开了一阵子 但现在我又回来了
Been away, but now I'm back.
晚安 特朗斯先生
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
见到你真好
It's good to see you.
回来真不错 罗伊德
It's good to be back, Lloyd.
来点什么呢 先生?
What'll it be, sir?
那只咬过我的狗 它身上的毛 (注: 以毒攻毒之意)
Hair of the dog that bit me.
加冰的波本酒
Bourbon on the rocks.
就这么办
That'll do her.
不收您的钱 特朗斯先生
No charge to you, Mr. Torrance.
不收钱?
No charge?
您的钱在这里用不上
Your money's no good here.
是房子的命令
Orders from the house.
房子的命令
喝光吧 特朗斯先生
Drink up, Mr. Torrance.
我是那种喜欢知道 是谁在帮谁买酒的人 罗伊德
I'm the kind of man likes to know who's buying their drinks, Lloyd.
那与你无关 特朗斯先生
It's not a matter that concerns you, Mr. Torrance.
至少 在这点上无关
At least, not at this point.
随你怎么说 罗伊德
Anything you say, Lloyd.
随你怎么说
Anything you say.
噢 天啊! 我真的很抱歉 先生
Oh, dear! I'm so sorry, sir.
噢 我的天!
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
我把您的夹克弄得一团糟 先生
I've made an awful mess of your jacket, sir.
没关系 我有很多的夹克
That's all right. I've got plenty of jackets.
但这是蛋酒 先生 它常常会留下污点
I'm afraid it's advocaat, sir. It tends to stain.
蛋酒 是吗?
Advocaat, is it?
是的 先生 我想最好的办法...
Yes, sir. I think the best thing...
就是去男洗手间...
...is to come along to the gentlemen's room...
然后我们用水擦一下 先生
...and we'll get some water to it, sir.
看起来好像你身上也沾了一点...
Looks like you might have got a spot of it on yourself...
杰佛西老伙计
...Jeevesy old boy.
那没关系 先生 您比较重要
That doesn't matter, sir. You're the important one.
你这么说真是太好了
Awfully nice of you to say.
当然 我想过在晚会前
Of course, I intended to change my jacket this evening...
换件夹克...
...before the fish and goose soiree.
很明智 先生 非常明智
Very wise, sir. Very wise.
这儿 我帮你...
Here. I'll just...
拿着这个 杰佛西
...hold this for you there, Jeevesy.
先生 谢谢
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
看看沾点水是不是会好些 先生
Let's see if we can improve this with a little water, sir.
好吧 我把...
All right. I'll just...
我的波本酒和蛋酒放在这儿
...set my bourbon and advocaat down right there.
耽误不了您不多久时间
Won't keep you a moment.
好
Fine.
他们是怎么叫你的呢 杰佛西?
What do they call you, Jeevesy?
格瑞第 先生 戴伯特·格瑞第
Grady, sir. Delbert Grady.
格瑞第?
Grady?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
戴伯特·格瑞第
Delbert Grady.
对 先生
That's right, sir.
格瑞第先生...
Mr. Grady...
我该不会以前在哪儿见过你吧?
...haven't I seen you somewhere before?
为什么...? 不是 先生 我不这么认为
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
擦掉了 先生
It's coming off now, sir.
格瑞第先生...
Mr. Grady...
你不是曾经担任过这里的看管员吗?
...weren't you once the caretaker here?
为什么...? 不是 先生 我不这么认为
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
你结婚了 是吗 格瑞第先生?
You a married man, are you, Mr. Grady?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
我有妻子和两个女儿 先生
I have a wife and two daughters, sir.
那...
And...
她们现在在哪里?
...where are they now?
她们就在附近的某个地方 我现在也不能确定
They're somewhere around. I'm not quite sure at the moment.
格瑞第先生...
Mr. Grady...
你曾是这里的看管员
You were the caretaker here.
我认出你了
I recognize you.
我在报纸上看到过你的照片
I saw your picture in the newspapers.
你...
You...
把你的妻子和女儿剁成碎片
...chopped your wife and daughter up into little bits.
然后...
And...
你把你自己的脑袋轰掉了
...then you blew your brains out.
那真奇怪 先生
That's strange, sir.
我对这个完全没有一点印象
I don't have any recollection of that at all.
格瑞第先生...
Mr. Grady...
你曾是这里的看管员
...you were the caretaker here.
很抱歉我和你不一样 先生
I'm sorry to differ with you, sir.
但是你...
But you...
才是看管员
...are the caretaker.
你一直都是看管员
You've always been the caretaker.
我应该知道 先生
I should know, sir.
我一直都在这里
I've always been here.
你知道吗 特朗斯先生...
Did you know, Mr. Torrance...
你的儿子...
...that your son...
正试图带外面的一帮人...
...is attempting to bring an outside party...
加入到这里来?
...into this situation?
你知道这个吗?
Did you know that?
他正是 特朗斯先生
He is, Mr. Torrance.
谁?
Who?
一个黑鬼
A nigger.
一个黑鬼?
A nigger?
一个黑鬼...
A nigger...
厨子
...cook.
怎么带法?
How?
你的儿子...
Your son...
有一种非常好的天赋
...has a very great talent.
我认为你都不知道那有多高
I don't think you are aware how great it is.
但他正在试图使用他的天赋...
But he is attempting to use that very talent...
用来反抗你的意旨
...against your will.
好...
Well...
他是个很任性的孩子
...he is a very willful boy.
他的确是 特朗斯先生
Indeed he is, Mr. Torrance.
一个非常任性的孩子
A very willful boy.
一个很...
A rather...
顽皮的孩子...
...naughty boy...
如果允许我大胆的说 先生
...if I may be so bold, sir.
那是她妈妈
It's his mother.
她...
She...
妨碍我
...interferes.
也许需要跟他们好好的...
Perhaps they need a good...
谈一谈
...talking-to.
如果...
If...
你不介意我这么说的话
...you don't mind my saying so.
也许...
Perhaps...
光谈还不够
...a bit more.
我的姑娘们 先生...
My girls, sir...
她们开始不喜欢遥望旅馆
...they didn't care for the Overlook at first.
其中一个最后偷了包火柴...
One of them actually stole a pack of matches...
想把旅馆烧了
...and tried to burn it down.
但是我...
But I...
纠正了她们 先生
...corrected them, sir.
当我的妻子阻止我 达成我的使命的时候...
And when my wife tried to prevent me from doing my duty...
我...
...I...
纠正了她
...corrected her.
我们有雪地车
We have the Snowcat.
如果天气稍微变好...
If the weather breaks...
我们就能...
...we might just be able...
下山去了
...to get down the mountain.
我可以先给林务员打电话...
I could call the forest rangers first...
告诉他们我们来了
...and...tell them that we're coming...
这样...
....so that...
如果我们后来没到达 他们就会来找我们
...they could start searching for us in case we didn't make it.
如果杰克不陪我们走的话...
And if Jack won't come with us...
我只有告诉他 我们自己走了
...I'll just have to tell him that we're going by ourselves.
就这么办了
That's all there is to it.
Redrum红酒 (注:谋杀-Murder的倒写)
Redrum.
Redrum红酒
怎么了 宝贝?
What's the matter, hon?
Redrum红酒!
Redrum!
你在做恶梦吗?
Are you having a bad dream?
宝贝?
Hon?
丹尼不在这儿 特朗斯太太
Danny's not here, Mrs. Torrance.
快点 宝贝
Come on, honey.
醒醒啊
Wake up.
你只是做了个恶梦
You just had a bad dream.
没事了
Everything's okay.
丹尼不能醒来了 特朗斯太太
Danny can't wake up, Mrs. Torrance.
醒醒!
Wake up!
快啊
Come on.
就现在
Right now.
醒醒!
Wake up!
丹尼离开了 特朗斯太太
Danny's gone away, Mrs. Torrance.
KDK 1 呼叫 KDK 12
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
你有收到吗?
Are you receiving me?
KDK 1 呼叫 KDK 12
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
听到我说话吗?
Do you read me?
KDK 1 呼叫 KDK 12
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
你有收到吗?
Are you receiving me?
晚安 森林服务台
Good evening. Forest service.
我还是迪克·霍洛朗
This is Dick Hallorann again.
我刚才打了电话联系遥望旅馆的人
I called a while ago about the folks at the Overlook Hotel.
我们试图联系他们多次 但都没有回应
We tried to contact them several times but they didn't answer.
可能他们没有开无线电 也可能是没听到
Maybe they got their radio turned off or they can't hear it.
如果你觉得有必要 我待会儿再呼叫他们
If you'd like, I'd be glad to try again later on.
你人真好
That's very nice of you.
我一会儿再打给你
I'll call you back later.
再见
Bye.
对不起 小姐 我们什么时候才能到丹佛?
Pardon me, miss. What time will we get to Denver?
预计是8点20分到达 先生
We're due to arrive at 8:20, sir.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
杜瑞凯的修车场
Durkin's Garage.
我找赖利
Can I speak to Larry?
请说
Speaking.
嗨 赖利 我是迪克 迪克·霍洛朗
Hi, Larry. This is Dick. Dick Hallorann.
迪克! 你好吗?
Dick! How you doing?
那边天气怎么样?
How's the weather down there?
我没在佛罗里达 我在斯塔普列顿机场给你打电话
I'm not in Florida. I'm calling from Stapleton Airport.
你在那儿干什么?
What are you doing there?
我刚从迈阿密来 我今天要去遥望旅馆
I just got in from Miami. I got to get to the Overlook today.
那里天气如何?
What's the weather like there?
扫雪机不断在运作 货物还是能运进城...
The snowplows are keeping things moving in town...
但是山路全被封死了
...but the mountain roads are blocked.
那我找辆雪地车上去
Then I'm going to need a Snowcat to get up there.
你能给我弄出一辆吗?
Can you fix me up with one?
出了什么大事 非得今天上那儿...?
What's the big deal about getting there today...
尤其是在这种天气?
...especially in this weather?
赖利 只在你我之间说说 我们遇上了很严重的问题...
Larry, just between you and me, we got a very serious problem...
关于看管那个地方的人
...with the people taking care of the place.
他们根本就在打混摸鱼
They turned out to be completely unreliable assholes.
尤尔曼先生昨晚给我打了电话
Ullman phoned me last night.
委派我去看看 是不是该把他们换掉! ?
And I'm supposed to find out if they have to be replaced.
要多久你才能到那里?
How long will it take you to get here?
大概五小时
About five hours.
我会在机场租辆车
I'm going to rent a car here at the airport.
好 雪地车我会想办法
Okay, I'll take care of it.
谢谢 赖利 我真的非常感激
Thanks, Larry. I really appreciate that.
就这样吧 开车小心些
That's all right. Drive carefully.
您正在收听的是丹佛63号电台 哈尔和查理为您播报
You're with Hal and Charlie on Radio 63, KHOW, Denver.
天气很糟
And we have a bad day out there.
丹佛市中区普降大雪
Heavy snow throughout the Denver metro area.
很多的入山关口...
Many mountain passes...
狼溪和红山的关口被关闭...
... Wolf Creek and Red Mountain passes are closed...
连带也影响了艾森豪威尔隧道
...and the chain law is in effect at the Eisenhower Tunnel.
我们从新闻部门获悉...
We hear from the news department...
只有少数几架飞机 降落在斯塔普列顿机场...
...only a few flights are landing at Stapleton Airport...
而且在这样的暴风雪天气...
...and with storms like this...
我想机场会在一个小时内 完全关闭
...I guess the entire airport will be closed within the hour.
暴风雪会持续一整天 气象局...
The storm will continue through the day and the Weather Service...
已发布了 针对所有丹佛城周边地区的...
...has declared a stockman's and traveler's advisory...
旅客和牧人的通告
...for all areas outlying the Denver metro region.
把乳牛关在棚里
Get the cows in the barn.
宝贝?
Hon?
听我说 就一分钟 好吗?
Listen to me for a minute, will you?
我要去和爸爸谈几分钟...
I'm just going to go and talk to Daddy for a few minutes...
我会很快回来
...and I'll be right back.
我要你就待在这儿...
I want you to just stay here...
看你的动画片 好吗?
...and watch your cartoons, okay?
好吗 宝贝?
Okay, hon?
好 特朗斯太太
Yes, Mrs. Torrance.
好
All right.
我大概只要五分钟就回来
I'll be back in just about five minutes.
我出去的时候会把门给锁上
I'm going to lock the door behind me.
只有工作 没有玩乐 杰克呆若木鸡!
你说好不好呢?
How do you like it?
好不好呢?
你在这下面做什么?
What are you doing down here?
我只是...
I just...
想...
...wanted...
和你谈谈
...to talk to you.
好
Okay.
那我们就谈吧
Let's talk.
你想谈什么呢?
What do you want to talk about?
我真的是记不得了
I can't really remember.
你记不得了
You can't remember.
不行...
No...
我不能
...I can't.
也许是关于丹尼?
Maybe it was about Danny?
也许是关于他
Maybe it was about him.
我想我们该讨论一下丹尼
I think we should discuss Danny.
我想...
I think...
我们该讨论一下 应该拿他怎么办才好
...we should discuss what should be done with him.
应该拿他怎么办?
What should be done with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
我认为那不是真的
I don't think that's true.
我想你有一些很明确的想法...
I think you have some very definite ideas...
关于应该拿丹尼怎么办
...about what should be done with Danny.
我想知道究竟是些什么
And I'd like to know what they are.
嗯 我...
Well, I...
我想也许该带他去看医生
...I think maybe he should be taken to a doctor.
你认为"也许"该带他去看医生?
You think "maybe" he should be taken to a doctor?
你是什么时候开始想 "也许"该带他去看医生的?
When do you think "maybe" he should be taken to a doctor?
尽快?
As soon as possible?
"尽快? "
"As soon as possible?"
求求你
Please.
你相信他的健康有严重问题?
You believe his health might be at stake.
是
Yes.
而且你很关心他
And you are concerned about him.
那你关心我吗?
And are you concerned about me?
我当然关心
Of course I am.
你当然关心!
Of course you are!
你可曾想过我的责任吗?
Have you ever thought about my responsibilities?
你在说些什么?
What are you talking about?
你有没有想过 就一分钟...
Have you ever had a single moment's...
想过我的责任?
...thought about my responsibilities?
有没有片刻想过...
Have you ever thought for a single moment...
我对我的雇主的责任? !
...about my responsibilities to my employers?!
我已经同意...
Has is ever occurred to you...
看管这座旅馆直到5月1号?
...that I have agreed to look after the hotel until May 1st?
它跟你有关系吗...
Does it matter to you at all...
就是主人完全信任我...
...that the owners have placed their complete confidence in me...
就是我签了契约...
...and that I have signed a letter of agreement...
在那里面我接受了委任?
...in which I've accepted that responsibility?
你是否有哪怕是最卑微的一点理解...
Do you have the slightest idea...
关于什么是伦理道德的精髓? 你有吗?
...what a moral and ethical principal is? Do you?!
你可曾想过 会对我的前途产生什么影响...
Has it ever occurred to you what would happen to my future...
如果我不能带着我的责任快乐的生活?
...if I fail to live up to my responsibilities?
你可曾想过那样的事? 可曾想过? !
Has it ever occurred to you? Has it?!
走开!
Stay away from me!
为什么?
Why?
我想回我的房间了
I just want to go back to my room.
为什么?
Why?
嗯...
Well...
我很困惑
...I'm very confused.
我需要找个机会把事情想清楚
And I just need a chance to think things over.
你可以用他妈的一辈子时间 去把事情想清楚!
You've had your whole fucking life to think things over!
现在这几分钟又怎么够用?
What good's a few minutes more going to do you now?
走开!
Stay away from me!
求求你!
Please!
别伤害我
Don't hurt me.
我不会伤害你
I'm not going to hurt you.
走开!
Stay away from me!
Stay away!
亲爱的
Darling.
我生命的亮光
Light of my life.
我不会伤害你
I'm not going to hurt you.
你不让我说完
You didn't let me finish my sentence.
我说: "我不会伤害你"
I said, "I'm not going to hurt you."
我只想锤你的头
I'm just going to bash your brains in.
我只想一边办事一边重锤
I'm going to bash them right the fuck in.
走开!
Stay away from me!
我不会伤害你
I'm not going to hurt you.
走开!
Stay away from me!
Stay away!
求求你!
Please!
别挥那根球棒!
Stop swinging the bat.
走开
Stay away from me.
把那根球棒放下 温蒂
Put that bat down, Wendy.
停下来!
Stop it!
把球棒给我
Give me the bat.
求求你!
Please!
- 走开! - 把球棒给我
- Stay away! - Give me the bat.
停!
Stop it!
把球棒给我
Give me the bat.
- 走开 - 球棒别乱挥
- Stay away from me. - Stop swinging the bat.
求求你停下来
Please stop!
把球棒给我
Give me the bat.
走开
Stay away from me.
- 停下来! - 把球棒给我
- Stop it! - Give me the bat.
见鬼!
Goddamn!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
等一下
Wait a minute.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
等一下
Wait a minute!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
开门
Open the door!
见鬼!
Goddamn it!
让我出去! 开门!
Let me out of here! Open the goddamn door!
温蒂 听着
Wendy, listen.
让我出去 我会把整件事忘掉
Let me out and I'll forget the whole goddamn thing.
就当什么也没有发生过
It'll be just like nothing ever happened.
宝贝
Baby.
我想你真的对我的头下了重手
I think you hurt my head real bad.
我头昏
I'm dizzy.
我需要个医生
I need a doctor.
甜心
Honey.
别把我留在这儿
Don't leave me in here.
我现在要走了
I'm going to go now.
我今天要...
I'm going to try...
用雪地车带丹尼下山...
...to get Danny down the Sidewinder...in the Snowcat today.
我会带个医生回来
I'll bring back a doctor.
温蒂
Wendy.
我现在要走了
I'm going to go now.
- 温蒂 - 干嘛?
- Wendy. - yes?
你会有个大惊喜
You've got a big surprise coming to you.
你哪儿都去不了
You're not going anywhere.
去看看雪地车吧 还有无线电 你会明白我的意思的
Go check out the Snowcat and the radio, and you'll see what I mean.
去看看
Go check it out.
去看看!
Go check it out!
去看看
Go check it out.
我是格瑞第 特朗斯先生
It's Grady, Mr. Torrance.
德尔伯特·格瑞第
Delbert Grady.
格瑞第?
Grady?
你好 格瑞第
Hello, Grady.
特朗斯先生...
Mr. Torrance...
我看你很难办好...
...I see you can hardly have taken care of the...
我们先前讨论的事
...business we discussed.
没有必要说第二遍 格瑞第先生
No need to rub it in, Mr. Grady.
只要我一出去 就会处理现在的情况
I'll deal with that situation as soon as I get out of here.
你确实会 特朗斯先生?
Will you indeed, Mr. Torrance?
我想知道
I wonder.
我有几个疑点
I have my doubts.
我 还有其他人 都相信...
I, and others, have come to believe...
你的心没在这里
...that your heart is not in this.
你对它没胃口
That you haven't the belly for it.
再给我个机会证明它 格瑞第先生
Just give me one more chance to prove it, Mr. Grady.
那是我全部的要求
That's all I ask.
你的妻子看来比我们想像要来得强 特朗斯先生
Your wife appears to be stronger than we imagined, Mr. Torrance.
要更...
Somewhat more...
机灵一点
...resourceful.
好像她胜过你
She seems to have got the better of you.
就这一会儿 格瑞第先生
For the moment, Mr. Grady.
就只这一会儿
Only for the moment.
我怕你得用一种最粗野的方式...
I fear you will have to deal with this matter...
来处理这件事 特朗斯先生
...in the harshest possible way, Mr. Torrance.
我怕...
I fear...
这是唯一可做的事了
...that is the only thing to do.
再没有比这...
There's nothing I look forward to...
更让人愉快的事 格瑞第先生
...with greater pleasure, Mr. Grady.
你保证 不是吗 特朗斯先生?
You give your word on that, do you, Mr. Torrance?
我向你保证
I give you my word.
Redrum红酒 (注:Murder谋杀的倒写)
Redrum.
Redrum红酒
丹尼 别这样!
Danny, stop it!
我回家了
I'm home.
出来 出来 不管你在哪儿
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
我出不去
I can't get out.
快跑!
Run!
快跑 躲起来!
Run and hide!
快跑!
Run!
快!
Quick!
小猪 小猪 让我进去
Little pigs, little pigs, let me come in.
不用你下巴上的毛?
Not by the hair on your chinny-chin-chin?
然后我要生气了...
Then I'll huff...
接着我要喘气了...
...and I'll puff...
然后我要毁了你的房子 冲进去!
...and I'll blow your house in!
求求你!
Please!
不要!
Don't!
停下来!
Stop it!
强尼来了!
Here's Johnny!
喂?
Hello?
有人在吗?
Anybody here?
喂?
Hello?
有人在吗?
Anybody here?
丹尼男孩!
Danny-boy!
我来了!
I'm coming!
我来了 小丹!
I'm coming, Dan!
爽死人的宴会 不是吗?
Great party, isn't it?
我来了!
I'm coming!
你逃不掉的!
You can't get away!
我就在你后面!
I'm right behind you!
- 妈咪! - 丹尼 到这儿来!
- Mommy! - Danny, come here!
妈咪
Mommy.
你在哪...?
Where...?
温蒂!
Wendy!
等等!
Wait!
不要!
No!
救命!
Help!
温蒂!
Wendy!
救救我!
Help!
求你...
Please...
温蒂
Wendy.
救命
Help.
求求你
Please.
遥望旅馆1921年7月4日舞会